if-not-true-then-false.com 2019-07-13

# Privacy Policy – If Not True Then False

### About this site

This website name is **If Not True Then False** and webite address is: https://www.if-not-true-then-false.com.

We respect your privacy and protect the Personal Data we collect. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you of how we protect your privacy when accessing or using our resources.

### What information do we collect?

We collect and log your IP address, the timestamp of your visit (page load), page address and information about your computer system, such as your browser type and operating system, whenever our Resource is accessed or used by you.

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form or leave a comment.

When commenting or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or website address.

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

### 3rd Party Advertisements

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

### Analytics

We also collects anonymous usage information on Visitors to its website through use of [Google Analytics](https://policies.google.com/privacy). Google Analytics may employ third party tracking cookies to gather anonymous browser, operating system, geographic, and website navigation information.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

– To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

– To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

### Who we share your data with

Your DNS and other requests go through [CloudFlare services](https://www.cloudflare.com/privacypolicy/). Your comments may be checked through [AKISMET spam detection service](https://automattic.com/privacy/). Ads are served using [Google Ads services](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads) and [BuySellAds services](https://www.buysellads.com/about/privacy). Also we collect anonymous usage information on visitors through [Google Analytics](https://policies.google.com/privacy). Your Social Media shares go through [AddThis service](https://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy/). Third party services (CloudFlare, Akismet, Google Ads, Google Analytics, AddThis) may employ tracking cookies to gather anonymous browser, operating system, geographic, and website navigation information.

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

### Contact information

If you have further questions regarding this Privacy Policy or your data please contact us via email [info@if-not-true-then-false.com](mailto:info@if-not-true-then-false.com).

Published: Nov 8, 2011 | Updated: May 19, 2018 | by
